Haocen Jiang

University of Waterloo, Waterloo, Ontario, Canada haocen.jiang@uwaterloo.ca www.haocenj.com

OBJECTIVE

To request for a Co-op position or research opportunity that gives me the chance to utilize my programming skills and problem-solving ability, as well as to explore and observe the practical aspects of programming and computation in order to further develop my visions and abilities in the field of computer science.

SKILLS

Programming:

(Proficient in) C, HTML/CSS, Scheme; (Familiar with) R/Python, JavaScript, Node.JS, Mongo;

Technologies:

(Proficient in) Office, LaTeX, Adobe InDesign/Photoshop; (Familiar with) MySQL, MongoDB, Git;

Additional:

(Proficient in) Mandarin, Photography;

EXPERIENCE

Mathematics Society / University of Waterloo

2017.09 - present

Worked in the Mathematics Society Office on the office routines. Provided services and help to students of the faculty.

Yearbook Chief Editor / Sino-Canada High School

2015.09 - 2017.06

Designed, edited, and organized pages of the yearbook using Adobe InDesign and Adobe Photoshop. Assisted in creating polls and collecting data from students for suggestions and analysis.

Graduation Banquet Committee Member / Sino-Canada High School 2017.03 – 2017.06

Utilized office excel for collecting student/teacher information, agenda setting and funding management. Negotiated with bus companies, hotel managers, souvenir producers, etc.

Survey Analysis / Sino-Canada High School

2016.09 - 2017.02

- present

Designed and created surveys on Surveymonkey.com with respect to various kinds of bullying on campus. Assisted in analyzing the data from the statistical point of view.

EDUCATION

University of Waterloo, Waterloo, Ontario, Canada	2017.09
---	---------

Honor Bachelor of Mathematics Candidate (GPA: 90%, Major Average: 92%)

Sino-Canada high school / Suzhou, Jiangsu, china. 2014.09 – 2017.06

Graduation with Honor (Grade12 GPA: 94%)

HONORS:

Term Dean's Honor List: University of Waterloo (Fall 2017)	2018
University of Waterloo President Scholarship: University of Waterloo	2018
Graduation with Honor: Sino-Canada High School, Top10 GPA	2017
Euclid Mathematics Contest: Honor of Distinction	2017